Finding aid to the Athletics Subject Files CA.MS.00167
Smith College Archives
- Hockey, Field
  - Hockey, Field, 1939 (Box 1359, Folder 14)
  - Hockey, Field, 1940-1945 (Box 1359, Folder 15)
  - Hockey, Field, 1947 (Box 1359, Folder 16)
  - Hockey, Field, 1949 (Box 1359, Folder 17)
  - Hockey, Field, 1950 (Box 1359, Folder 18)
  - Hockey, Field, 1951-1954 (Box 1359, Folder 19)
  - Hockey, Field, 1961-1965 (Box 1359, Folder 20)
  - Hockey, Field, 1965-1970 (Box 1359, Folder 21)
  - Hockey, Field, 1970s (Box 1359, Folder 22)
  - Hockey, Field, 1980-1983 (Box 1359, Folder 23)
  - Hockey, Field, 1983-1984 (Box 1359, Folder 24)
  - Hockey, Field, 1984-1985 (Box 1359, Folder 25)
  - Hockey, Field, 1985-1986 (Box 1359, Folder 26)
  - Hockey, Field, 1986-1987 (Box 1359, Folder 27)
  - Hockey, Field, 1987-1988 (Box 1359, Folder 28)
  - Hockey, Field, 1988-1989 (Box 1359, Folder 29)
  - Hockey, Field, 1989-1990 (Box 1359, Folder 30)
  - Hockey, Field, 1990-1992 (Box 1359, Folder 31)
  - Hockey, Field, 1992-1993 (Box 1360, Folder 1)
  - Hockey, Field, 1993-1994 (Box 1360, Folder 2)
  - Hockey, Field, 1994-1995 (Box 1360, Folder 3)
  - Hockey, Field, 1995-1997 (Box 1360, Folder 4)
  - Hockey, Field, 1997-1998 (Box 1360, Folder 5)
  - Hockey, Field, 1999-2000 (Box 1360, Folder 6)
  - Hockey, Field, 2000-2002 (Box 1360, Folder 7)
  - Hockey, Field, 2004-ongoing (Box 1360, Folder 8)
  - Hockey, Field, undated (Box 1360, Folder 9)
  - Hockey, Field: Photos, undated (Box 1360, Folder 10)
  - Hockey, Field: Manager's Book, 1946-1974 (Box 1360, Folder 11)
  - Hockey, Field: Record Book, loose papers, 1916-1969 (Box 1360, Folder 12)
  - Hockey, Field: Record Book, 1916-1930 (Box 1360, Folder 13)
  - Hockey, Field: Record Book, 1931-1969 (Box 1360, Folder 14)
  - Hockey, Field: Record Book, 1969-1980 (Box 1360, Folder 15)
- Hockey, Ice, 1997-ongoing (Box 1360, Folder 16)
- Homecoming, 1989 (Box 1360, Folder 17)
- Human Performance Lab, 1978 (Box 1360, Folder 18)
- Intramural Indoor Soccer, 1988-ongoing (Box 1361, Folder 1)
- Jack Stones, 1923 (Box 1361, Folder 2)
- Javelin, 1929-ongoing (Box 1361, Folder 3)
- Judo, 1966-ongoing (Box 1361, Folder 4)
- Jumping, 1928-1929 (Box 1361, Folder 5)
- Jumping, 1930-1935 (Box 1361, Folder 6)
- Jumping, undated (Box 1361, Folder 7)
- Karate, 1977 (Box 1361, Folder 8)
- Lacrosse
  - Lacrosse, 1929 (Box 1361, Folder 9)
  - Lacrosse, 1930 (Box 1361, Folder 10)
  - Lacrosse, 1931 (Box 1361, Folder 11)
  - Lacrosse, 1932 (Box 1361, Folder 12)
  - Lacrosse, 1934-1935 (Box 1361, Folder 13)
  - Lacrosse, 1936-1939 (Box 1361, Folder 14)
  - Lacrosse, 1940 (Box 1361, Folder 15)
  - Lacrosse, 1944-1946 (Box 1361, Folder 16)
  - Lacrosse, 1950-1952 (Box 1361, Folder 17)
  - Lacrosse, 1952-1953 (Box 1361, Folder 18)
  - Lacrosse, 1954-1960 (Box 1361, Folder 19)
  - Lacrosse, 1960s (Box 1361, Folder 20)
  - Lacrosse, 1970s (Box 1361, Folder 21)
  - Lacrosse: Record Book, 1931-1977 (Box 1361, Folder 22)
  - Lacrosse: Record Book, 1978-ongoing (Box 1361, Folder 23)
  - Lacrosse, 1980-1981 (Box 1362, Folder 1)
  - Lacrosse, 1981-1982 (Box 1362, Folder 2)
  - Lacrosse, 1982-1983 (Box 1362, Folder 3)
  - Lacrosse, 1983-1984 (Box 1362, Folder 4)
  - Lacrosse, 1984-1985 (Box 1362, Folder 5)
  - Lacrosse, 1985-1986 (Box 1362, Folder 6)
  - Lacrosse, 1986-1987 (Box 1362, Folder 7)
  - Lacrosse, 1987-1988 (Box 1362, Folder 8)
  - Lacrosse, 1988-1989 (Box 1362, Folder 9)
  - Lacrosse, 1989-1990 (Box 1362, Folder 10)
  - Lacrosse, 1990-1991 (Box 1362, Folder 11)
  - Lacrosse, 1991-1994 (Box 1362, Folder 12)
  - Lacrosse, 1993-1994 (Box 1362, Folder 13)
  - Lacrosse, 1994-1995 (Box 1362, Folder 14)
  - Lacrosse, 1995-1997 (Box 1362, Folder 15)
  - Lacrosse, 1997-1998 (Box 1362, Folder 16)
  - Lacrosse, 1999-2000 (Box 1362, Folder 17)
  - Lacrosse, 2000-2002 (Box 1362, Folder 18)
  - Lacrosse, 2003-ongoing (Box 1362, Folder 19)
  - Lacrosse: photos, undated (Box 1362, Folder 20)
  - Lacrosse: handbooks and scrapbooks, 1945-1970 (Box 1362.1)
- Outing Club
  - Outing Club, 1922-1926 (Box 1363, Folder 1)
  - Outing Club, 1927-1928 (Box 1363, Folder 2)
  - Outing Club, 1929-1930 (Box 1363, Folder 3)
  - Outing Club, 1931-1932 (Box 1363, Folder 4)
  - Outing Club, 1933-1939 (Box 1363, Folder 5)
  - Outing Club, 1940-1946 (Box 1363, Folder 6)
  - Outing Club, 1947-1949 (Box 1363, Folder 7)
  - Outing Club, 1950s (Box 1363, Folder 8)
  - Outing Club, 1960-1961 (Box 1363, Folder 9)
  - Outing Club, 1963-1968 (Box 1363, Folder 10)
  - Outing Club, 1974-1977 (Box 1363, Folder 11)
  - Outing Club, 1977-ongoing (Box 1363, Folder 12)
  - Outing Club: Constitution, 1929-1959 (Box 1363, Folder 13)
  - Outing Club: Handbook, 1955 (Box 1363, Folder 14)
  - Outing Club: Journals, Record books, 1920-1931 (Box 1363, Folder 15)
  - Outing Club: Newsletter, 1988 (Box 1363, Folder 16)
  - Outing Club: Photos and papers, undated (Box 1363, Folder 17)
  - Outing Club
    - IOCA Bulletin, 1934-1960 (Box 1363.1, Folder 1)
    - IOCA Bulletin, 1961-1962 (Box 1363.1, Folder 2)
    - IOCA Bulletin, 1963-1964 (Box 1363.1, Folder 3)
    - IOCA Bulletin, miscellaneous pamphlets, 1965-1968 (Box 1363.1, Folder 4)
  - Outing Club: scrapbook, 1930-1940 (Box 1363.2)
- Ping Pong, 1929-1939 (Box 1364, Folder 1)
- Polo, 1925 (Box 1364, Folder 2)
- Riding
  - Riding: History at Smith, 1954 (Box 1364, Folder 3)
  - Riding, 1912-1913 (Box 1364, Folder 4)
  - Riding, 1927-1929 (Box 1364, Folder 5)
  - Riding, 1929 (Box 1364, Folder 6)
  - Riding, 1930 (Box 1364, Folder 7)
  - Riding, 1931 (Box 1364, Folder 8)
  - Riding, 1932 (Box 1364, Folder 9)
  - Riding, 1933 (Box 1364, Folder 10)
  - Riding, 1934 (Box 1364, Folder 11)
  - Riding, 1935 (Box 1364, Folder 12)
  - Riding, 1936 (Box 1364, Folder 13)
  - Riding, 1937 (Box 1364, Folder 14)
  - Riding, 1938 (Box 1364, Folder 15)
  - Riding, 1939 (Box 1364, Folder 16)
  - Riding, 1940 (Box 1364, Folder 17)
  - Riding, 1941 (Box 1364, Folder 18)
  - Riding, 1944 (Box 1364, Folder 19)
  - Riding, 1945 (Box 1364, Folder 20)
  - Riding, 1947 (Box 1364, Folder 21)
  - Riding, 1948 (Box 1364, Folder 22)
  - Riding, 1949 (Box 1364, Folder 23)
  - Riding, 1950 (Box 1364, Folder 24)
  - Riding, 1951 (Box 1364, Folder 25)
  - Riding, 1953 (Box 1364, Folder 26)
  - Riding, 1953-1954 (Box 1364, Folder 27)
  - Riding, 1954 (Box 1364, Folder 28)
  - Riding, 1954-1956 (Box 1364, Folder 29)
  - Riding, 1957 (Box 1364, Folder 30)
  - Riding, 1960s (Box 1364, Folder 31)
  - Riding, 1970 (Box 1364, Folder 32)
  - Riding, 1980-1983 (Box 1364, Folder 33)
  - Riding, 1983-1984 (Box 1364, Folder 34)
  - Riding, 1984-1985 (Box 1364, Folder 35)
  - Riding, 1985-1986 (Box 1364, Folder 36)
  - Riding, 1987-1988 (Box 1364, Folder 37)
  - Riding, 1988-1989 (Box 1364, Folder 38)
  - Riding, 1989-1990 (Box 1364, Folder 39)
  - Riding, 1990-1991 (Box 1364, Folder 40)
  - Riding, 1991-1993 (Box 1364, Folder 41)
  - Riding, 1993-1994 (Box 1365, Folder 1)
  - Riding, 1994-1995 (Box 1365, Folder 2)
  - Riding, 1995-1997 (Box 1365, Folder 3)
  - Riding, 1998-ongoing (Box 1365, Folder 4)
  - Riding, undated (Box 1365, Folder 5)
  - Riding: President's Report, 1966-67 (Box 1365, Folder 6)
  - Riding Club: Sports Report, 1965-1966 (Box 1365, Folder 7)
  - Riding Club: Sports Report, 1966-1967 (Box 1365, Folder 8)
  - Riding Club: Sports Report, 1967-1968 (Box 1365, Folder 9)
  - Riding Club: Sports Report, 1968-1969 (Box 1365, Folder 10)
  - Riding Club: Sports Report, 1969-1970 (Box 1365, Folder 11)
  - Riding: Record Book, 1931-1944 (Box 1366, Folder 1)
  - Riding: Record Book, 1945-1958 (Box 1366, Folder 2)
  - Riding: Record Book, 1958-1965 (Box 1366, Folder 3)
  - Riding: Record Book, 1970-1975 (Box 1367, Folder 1)
- Roller-skating, 1909-1923 (Box 1367, Folder 2)
- Rope Skipping, 1924; undated (Box 1367, Folder 3)
- Rugby, 1979-1999 (Box 1367, Folder 4)
- Running, 1977 (Box 1367, Folder 5)
- "S"
  - "S" Club, undated (Box 1367, Folder 6)
  - "S" Pins: descriptions and clippings, 1911-1968 (Box 1367, Folder 7)
  - "S" Pins: photos, 1926-1958 (Box 1367, Folder 8)
  - "S" Sweaters, 1911-1922 (Box 1367, Folder 9)
- Sailing, 1960-ongoing (Box 1367, Folder 10)
- Sailing, undated (Box 1367, Folder 11)
- Sailing: Record Book, 1961-1977 (Box 1367, Folder 12)
- Shooting, 1935 (Box 1368, Folder 1)
- Skating
  - Skating, 1800s-1900s (Box 1368, Folder 2)
  - Skating, 1900-1920 (Box 1368, Folder 3)
  - Skating, 1928-1933 (Box 1368, Folder 4)
  - Skating, 1937-1940 (Box 1368, Folder 5)
  - Skating, 1946-ongoing (Box 1368, Folder 6)
  - Skating: photos, undated (Box 1368, Folder 7)
  - Skating: Record Book, 1966-1976 (Box 1368, Folder 8)
- Skiing
  - Skiing, 1920-1921 (Box 1368, Folder 9)
  - Skiing, 1930-1935 (Box 1368, Folder 10)
  - Skiing, 1935-1936 (Box 1368, Folder 11)
  - Skiing, 1936-1937 (Box 1368, Folder 12)
  - Skiing, 1938-1940 (Box 1368, Folder 13)
  - Skiing, 1941-1942 (Box 1368, Folder 14)
  - Skiing, 1944-1945 (Box 1368, Folder 15)
  - Skiing, 1945-1946 (Box 1368, Folder 16)
  - Skiing, 1946-1949 (Box 1368, Folder 17)
  - Skiing, 1949-1950 (Box 1368, Folder 18)
  - Skiing, 1950-1951 (Box 1368, Folder 19)
  - Skiing, 1951-1953 (Box 1368, Folder 20)
  - Skiing, 1954-1978 (Box 1368, Folder 21)
  - Skiing, 1981-1982 (Box 1368, Folder 22)
  - Skiing, 1982-1983 (Box 1368, Folder 23)
  - Skiing, 1983-1984 (Box 1368, Folder 24)
  - Skiing, 1984-1985 (Box 1368, Folder 25)
  - Skiing, 1985-1986 (Box 1368, Folder 26)
  - Skiing, 1986-1987 (Box 1368, Folder 27)
  - Skiing, 1987-1988 (Box 1368, Folder 28)
  - Skiing, 1988-1989 (Box 1368, Folder 29)
  - Skiiing, 1989-1900 (Box 1368.1, Folder 1)
  - Skiing, 1990-1992 (Box 1368.1, Folder 2)
  - Skiing, 1992-1994 (Box 1368.1, Folder 3)
  - Skiing, 1994-1995 (Box 1368.1, Folder 4)
  - Skiing, 1995-1997 (Box 1368.1, Folder 5)
  - Skiing, 1997-ongoing (Box 1368.1, Folder 6)
  - Skiing: Photos, undated (Box 1368.1, Folder 7)
  - Skiing: Record Book, 1948-1978 (Box 1368.1, Folder 8)
- Sledding, 1911-1924 (Box 1368.1, Folder 9)
- Snowball Fights, 1890s-1925 (Box 1368.1, Folder 10)
- Snow Sculpture, 1898-1955 (Box 1368.1, Folder 11)
- Snow Shoeing, 1895-1919 (Box 1368.1, Folder 12)
- Snow Sports, 1897-1962 (Box 1368.1, Folder 13)
- Soccer
  - Soccer, 1920 (Box 1369, Folder 1)
  - Soccer, 1932-1933 (Box 1369, Folder 2)
  - Soccer, 1934-1936 (Box 1369, Folder 3)
  - Soccer, 1937 (Box 1369, Folder 4)
  - Soccer, 1938 (Box 1369, Folder 5)
  - Soccer, 1939 (Box 1369, Folder 6)
  - Soccer, 1940 (Box 1369, Folder 7)
  - Soccer, 1950 (Box 1369, Folder 8)
  - Soccer, 1951 (Box 1369, Folder 9)
  - Soccer, 1952-1953 (Box 1369, Folder 10)
  - Soccer, 1965-1966 (Box 1369, Folder 11)
  - Soccer, 1976-1978 (Box 1369, Folder 12)
  - Soccer, 1979-1980 (Box 1369, Folder 13)
  - Soccer, 1981-1982 (Box 1369, Folder 14)
  - Soccer, 1982-1983 (Box 1369, Folder 15)
  - Soccer, 1983-1984 (Box 1369, Folder 16)
  - Soccer, 1984-1985 (Box 1369, Folder 17)
  - Soccer, 1985-1986 (Box 1369, Folder 18)
  - Soccer: Record Book, 1924-1979 (Box 1369, Folder 19)
  - Soccer, 1986-1987 (Box 1370, Folder 1)
  - Soccer, 1987-1988 (Box 1370, Folder 2)
  - Soccer, 1988-1989 (Box 1370, Folder 3)
  - Soccer, 1989-1990 (Box 1370, Folder 4)
  - Soccer, 1990-1993 (Box 1370, Folder 5)
  - Soccer, 1991-1992 (Box 1370, Folder 6)
  - Soccer, 1993-1994 (Box 1370, Folder 7)
  - Soccer, 1994-1995 (Box 1370, Folder 8)
  - Soccer, 1995-1997 (Box 1370, Folder 9)
  - Soccer, 1999-2000 (Box 1370, Folder 10)
  - Soccer, 2000-ongoing (Box 1370, Folder 11)
  - Soccer: Photos, undated (Box 1370, Folder 12)
  - Smith soccer team photographs with Abby Wambach, 2016 May; 2017-A-0139; 8.77 Megabytes; 8 items
    Scope and Contents
    Digital images of the 2015-2016 Smith Soccer members with soccer star Abby Wambach and "the Abby head" at convocation, and when she came to speak to the Athletic Department before Graduation, 2016.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access files will need to be created
    Wambach, Abby, 1980-
- Softball
  - Softball: General (Box 1370, Folder 13)
  - Softball: Photographs, 1960-1995 (Box 1370, Folder 14)
  - Softball: Record Book, 1948-1980 (Box 1370, Folder 15)
  - Softball, 2004-ongoing (Box 1370, Folder 16)
- Squash
  - Squash, 1920s-1930s (Box 1370, Folder 17)
  - Squash, 1940s (Box 1370, Folder 18)
  - Squash, 1950s (Box 1370, Folder 19)
  - Squash, 1960s (Box 1371, Folder 1)
  - Squash, 1970s (Box 1371, Folder 2)
  - Squash, 1980-1981 (Box 1371, Folder 3)
  - Squash, 1981-1982 (Box 1371, Folder 4)
  - Squash, 1982-1983 (Box 1371, Folder 5)
  - Squash, 1983-1984 (Box 1371, Folder 6)
  - Squash, 1984-1985 (Box 1371, Folder 7)
  - Squash, 1985-1986 (Box 1371, Folder 8)
  - Squash, 1986-1897 (Box 1371, Folder 9)
  - Squash, 1987-1988 (Box 1371, Folder 10)
  - Squash, 1988-1989 (Box 1371, Folder 11)
  - Squash, 1989-1990 (Box 1371, Folder 12)
  - Squash, 1990-1993 (Box 1371, Folder 13)
  - Squash, 1993-1994 (Box 1371, Folder 14)
  - Squash, 1994-1995 (Box 1371, Folder 15)
  - Squash, 1995-ongoing (Box 1371, Folder 16)
  - Squash: Photos, undated (Box 1371, Folder 17)
  - Squash: Record Book, 1934-1973 (Box 1371, Folder 18)
  - Squash: Record Book, 1973-1983 (Box 1371, Folder 19)
  - Squash: Regulations for Court Use, undated (Box 1371, Folder 20)
- Swimming and Diving
  - Swimming and Diving: General (Box 1372, Folder 1)
  - Swimming and Diving, Pre-1900 (Box 1372, Folder 2)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1927-1928 (Box 1372, Folder 3)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1928-1929 (Box 1372, Folder 4)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1930-1931 (Box 1372, Folder 5)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1931-193 (Box 1372, Folder 6)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1932-1933 (Box 1372, Folder 7)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1933-1934 (Box 1372, Folder 8)
  - Swimming: Record Book, 1924-1962 (Box 1372, Folder 9)
  - Swimming: Record Book, 1962-1982 (Box 1372, Folder 10)
  - Swimming: Record Book- removals pp. 1-27, 1962-1982 (Box 1372, Folder 11)
  - Swimming: Record Book- removals pp. 29-53, 1962-1982 (Box 1372, Folder 12)
  - Swimming: Record Book- removals pp. 61-75, 1962-1982 (Box 1372, Folder 13)
  - Swimming: Record Book- removals pp. 77-113, 1962-1982 (Box 1372, Folder 14)
  - Swimming: Record Book- removals pp. 120-133, 1962-1982 (Box 1372, Folder 15)
  - Swimming- Life Guards: Record Book, 1943-1950 (Box 1372, Folder 16)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1934-1935 (Box 1373, Folder 1)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1935-1936 (Box 1373, Folder 2)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1936-1937 (Box 1373, Folder 3)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1936-1938 (Box 1373, Folder 4)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1938-1939 (Box 1373, Folder 5)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1939-1940 (Box 1373, Folder 6)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1940-1941 (Box 1373, Folder 7)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1941-1942 (Box 1373, Folder 8)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1942-1943 (Box 1373, Folder 9)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1944 (Box 1373, Folder 10)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1945 (Box 1373, Folder 11)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1945-1946 (Box 1373, Folder 12)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1946-1948 (Box 1373, Folder 13)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1948-1949 (Box 1373, Folder 14)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1949-1950 (Box 1373, Folder 15)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1950-1951 (Box 1373, Folder 16)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1951-1953 (Box 1373, Folder 17)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1954-1957 (Box 1373, Folder 18)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1958-1959 (Box 1373, Folder 19)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1960 (Box 1373, Folder 20)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1970-1977 (Box 1373, Folder 21)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1977-1978 (Box 1373, Folder 22)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1978-1979 (Box 1373, Folder 23)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1979-1980 (Box 1373, Folder 24)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1980-1981 (Box 1373, Folder 25)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1981-1982 (Box 1373, Folder 26)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1982-1983 (Box 1373, Folder 27)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1983-1984 (Box 1373, Folder 28)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1984-1985 (Box 1373, Folder 29)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1985-1986 (Box 1373, Folder 30)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1986-1987 (Box 1373, Folder 31)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1987-1988 (Box 1373, Folder 32)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1988-1989 (Box 1373, Folder 33)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1989-1990 (Box 1373, Folder 34)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1990-1994 (Box 1373.1, Folder 1)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1994-ongoing (Box 1373.1, Folder 2)
  - Swimming and Diving, undated (Box 1373.1, Folder 3)
  - Swimming: Lifeguards, 1928-1994 (Box 1373.1, Folder 4)
  - Synchronized Swimming Club, 1994-ongoing (Box 1373.1, Folder 5)
- Tennis
  - Tennis, 1882-1883 (Box 1374, Folder 1)
  - Tennis, 1882-1883 (Box 1374, Folder 2)
  - Tennis, 1883 (Box 1374, Folder 3)
  - Tennis, 1884 (Box 1374, Folder 4)
  - Tennis, 1887-1891 (Box 1374, Folder 5)
  - Tennis, 1889 (Box 1374, Folder 6)
  - Tennis, 1890 (Box 1374, Folder 7)
  - Tennis, 1891 (Box 1374, Folder 8)
  - Tennis, 1892 (Box 1374, Folder 9)
  - Tennis, 1893 (Box 1374, Folder 10)
  - Tennis, 1894 (Box 1374, Folder 11)
  - Tennis, 1895 (Box 1374, Folder 12)
  - Tennis, 1896 (Box 1374, Folder 13)
  - Tennis, 1897 (Box 1374, Folder 14)
  - Tennis, 1898 (Box 1374, Folder 15)
  - Tennis, 1899 (Box 1374, Folder 16)
  - Tennis, 1900 (Box 1374, Folder 17)
  - Tennis, 1901 (Box 1374, Folder 18)
  - Tennis, 1902 (Box 1374, Folder 19)
  - Tennis, 1907-1908 (Box 1374, Folder 20)
  - Tennis, 1908-1909 (Box 1374, Folder 21)
  - Tennis, 1909-1910 (Box 1374, Folder 22)
  - Tennis, 1910-1911 (Box 1374, Folder 23)
  - Tennis, 1912-1913 (Box 1374, Folder 24)
  - Tennis, 1913-1914 (Box 1374, Folder 25)
  - Tennis, 1917-1918 (Box 1374, Folder 26)
  - Tennis, 1918-1919 (Box 1374, Folder 27)
  - Tennis, 1928-1929 (Box 1375, Folder 1)
  - Tennis, 1930-1931 (Box 1375, Folder 2)
  - Tennis, 1931-1932 (Box 1375, Folder 3)
  - Tennis, 1933-1934 (Box 1375, Folder 4)
  - Tennis, 1934-1935 (Box 1375, Folder 5)
  - Tennis, 1935-1936 (Box 1375, Folder 6)
  - Tennis, 1936-1937 (Box 1375, Folder 7)
  - Tennis, 1937-1938 (Box 1375, Folder 8)
  - Tennis, 1938-1939 (Box 1375, Folder 9)
  - Tennis, 1939-1940 (Box 1375, Folder 10)
  - Tennis, 1940-1944 (Box 1375, Folder 11)
  - Tennis, 1944-1945 (Box 1375, Folder 12)
  - Tennis, 1945-1949 (Box 1375, Folder 13)
  - Tennis, 1949-1950 (Box 1375, Folder 14)
  - Tennis, 1950s (Box 1375, Folder 15)
  - Tennis, 1960s (Box 1375, Folder 16)
  - Tennis, 1970s (Box 1375, Folder 17)
  - Tennis, 1980-1981 (Box 1375, Folder 18)
  - Tennis, 1981-1982 (Box 1375, Folder 19)
  - Tennis, 1981-1982 (Box 1375, Folder 20)
  - Tennis, 1982-1983 (Box 1375, Folder 21)
  - Tennis, 1983-1984 (Box 1375, Folder 22)
  - Tennis, 1984-1985 (Box 1375, Folder 23)
  - Tennis, 1985-1986 (Box 1375, Folder 24)
  - Tennis, 1986-1987 (Box 1375, Folder 25)
  - Tennis, 1987-1988 (Box 1375, Folder 26)
  - Tennis, 1988-1989 (Box 1375, Folder 27)
  - Tennis, 1989-1990 (Box 1375, Folder 28)
  - Tennis, 1990-1991 (Box 1375, Folder 29)
  - Tennis, 1991-1993 (Box 1375, Folder 30)
  - Tennis, 1993-1994 (Box 1375, Folder 31)
  - Tennis, 1994-1995 (Box 1376, Folder 1)
  - Tennis, 1995-1997 (Box 1376, Folder 2)
  - Tennis, 1997-2000 (Box 1376, Folder 3)
  - Tennis, 2000-ongoing (Box 1376, Folder 4)
  - Tennis: Photographs, undated (Box 1376, Folder 5)
  - Tennis: Record Books, 1927-1965 (Box 1376, Folder 6)
- Track
  - Track, 1920s (Box 1377, Folder 1)
  - Track, 1930s (Box 1377, Folder 2)
  - Track, 1980-1981 (Box 1377, Folder 3)
  - Track, 1981-1982 (Box 1377, Folder 4)
  - Track, 1983-1984 (Box 1377, Folder 5)
  - Track, 1984-1985 (Box 1377, Folder 6)
  - Track, 1985-1986 (Box 1377, Folder 7)
  - Track, 1986-1987 (Box 1377, Folder 8)
  - Track, 1987-1988 (Box 1377, Folder 9)
  - Track, 1988-1983 (Box 1377, Folder 10)
  - Track, 1989-1990 (Box 1377, Folder 11)
  - Track, 1990-1991 (Box 1377, Folder 12)
  - Track, 1991-1993 (Box 1377, Folder 13)
  - Track, 1993-1994 (Box 1377, Folder 14)
  - Track, 1994-1995 (Box 1377, Folder 15)
  - Track, 1999-2000 (Box 1377, Folder 16)
  - Track, 2000-2002 (Box 1377, Folder 17)
  - Track, 2004-ongoing (Box 1377, Folder 18)
  - Track: Photographs, undated (Box 1377, Folder 19)
  - Track: Record Book, 1962-1981 (Box 1377, Folder 20)
- Toboggan, 1898-1934 (Box 1377, Folder 21)
- Top Spinning, 1896 (Box 1377, Folder 22)
- Trampoline, 1961-1962 (Box 1377, Folder 23)
- Ultimate Frisbee, 1994-ongoing (Box 1377, Folder 24)
- Volleyball
  - Volleyball, 1911-1913 (Box 1377, Folder 25)
  - Volleyball, 1949-1950 (Box 1377, Folder 26)
  - Volleyball, 1951 (Box 1377, Folder 27)
  - Volleyball, 1952 (Box 1377, Folder 28)
  - Volleyball, 1954 (Box 1377, Folder 29)
  - Volleyball, 1960 (Box 1377, Folder 30)
  - Volleyball, 1970 (Box 1377, Folder 31)
  - Volleyball, 1979-1980 (Box 1377, Folder 32)
  - Volleyball: Record Book, 1913-1920 (Box 1377, Folder 33)
  - Volleyball, 1980-1981 (Box 1378, Folder 1)
  - Volleyball, 1981-1982 (Box 1378, Folder 2)
  - Volleyball, 1982-1983 (Box 1378, Folder 3)
  - Volleyball, 1983-1984 (Box 1378, Folder 4)
  - Volleyball, 1984-1985 (Box 1378, Folder 5)
  - Volleyball, 1985-1986 (Box 1378, Folder 6)
  - Volleyball, 1986-1987 (Box 1378, Folder 7)
  - Volleyball, 1987-1988 (Box 1378, Folder 8)
  - Volleyball, 1988-1989 (Box 1378, Folder 9)
  - Volleyball, 1989-1990 (Box 1378, Folder 10)
  - Volleyball, 1990-1993 (Box 1378, Folder 11)
  - Volleyball, 1993-1994 (Box 1378, Folder 12)
  - Volleyball, 1994-1995 (Box 1378, Folder 13)
  - Volleyball, 1995-1997 (Box 1378, Folder 14)
  - Volleyball, 1997-2003 (Box 1378, Folder 15)
  - Volleyball, 2004-ongoing (Box 1378, Folder 16)
  - Volleyball, undated (Box 1378, Folder 17)
- Walking Club, 1895-1897 (Box 1378, Folder 18)
- Winter Sports
  - Winter Sports, 1931 (Box 1378, Folder 19)
  - Winter Sports, 1934 (Box 1378, Folder 20)
  - Winter Sports, 1935 (Box 1378, Folder 21)
  - Winter Sports, 1936 (Box 1378, Folder 22)
  - Winter Sports, 1937 (Box 1378, Folder 23)
  - Winter Sports, 1939 (Box 1378, Folder 24)
  - Winter Sports, 1956-1957 (Box 1378, Folder 25)
- Williams, Roxane Lyn: Stronger and Saner